Guide to the Ed Smith Papers 1974-2005 (Bulk 1978-2004) MSS.177
Fales Library and Special Collections
Ed Smith Papers
1974-2005
1978-2004
Fales Library and Special Collections
Shirai, Mio, 1962-
Smith, Ed
MSS.177
8.5 Linear Feet (8 records cartons, 1 document case)
Ed Smith was a poet, active in the 1980's in the scene centered around the Beyond Baroque/Literary Arts Center in Los Angeles. His papers cover the period 1978-2005, when Smith lived in Los Angeles and New York City. The materials include, but are not limited to, journals, notebooks, correspondence, drafts, manuscripts, flyers, photographs, monographs and periodicals.
Provenance
The materials were created and/or assembled by Ed Smith, and donated to the Fales Library in 2006 by his wife Mio Shirai.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Ed Smith was born in Downey, California in 1957. He attended Pomona College in Claremont, California for one academic year (1975-76), before making his way to Los Angeles. He worked as a paralegal and for an independent record and video company, became interested in the punk scene, and then found his calling as a poet in the scene centered around the Beyond Baroque Literary/Arts Center in the 1980's. He published two collections of poetry, Fantasyworld (Venice, CA, Cold Calm Press, 1983)and Tim's Bunnies (Los Angeles, Cold Calm Press, 1988). His poems also appear in the collection Poetry Loves Poetry (Santa Monica, Momentum Press, 1985), and in various magazines. He practiced some journalism, writing articles and doing interviews for the magazine Shiny, of which he was also West Coast Editor, and for the L.A. Reader. To make ends meet, he worked as a typesetter, a movie ad copywriter, and as a math tutor at a private school. His friends and associates in the poetry scene included Dennis Cooper, Bob Flanagan. Other friends well represented by his papers include poets Amy Gerstler, Steven Hall, and Celia Pearce, musician Ingrid Baumgart, and video and performance artist Skip Arnold. He lived for periods of time with the latter two. After moving to New York City in the late 1990s and marrying artist Mio Shirai, Smith devoted himself to a business venture, CSAI, a consulting firm helping companies apply W. Edwards Demming's principles of emergent intelligence to their organizations. Smith battled depression for most of his life. In 2005, he committed suicide.
Scope and Content Note
The Ed Smith Papers are part of the Downtown Collection at Fales Library, New York University. The papers cover the period 1978-2005, when Smith lived in Los Angeles and New York City. The material is arranged into four series:
Series I: The Journals/Notebooks Series consists of spiral notebooks, bound notebooks, loose pages, and legal pads containing diary entries, drafts of poetry and correspondence, and business notes, arranged chronologically.
Series II: The Correspondence and Subject Series consists of interfiled correspondence folders and subject folders, arranged alphabetically (see arrangement note, below). The folders contain correspondence received by Ed Smith, flyers, photographs, and ephemera in chronological order. Some of the correspondents in his papers are former tutoring students.
Series III: The Drafts, Production Materials, and Final Published Work Series consists of published copies of Smith's books and articles, production material related to Tim's Bunnies, and draft material, including drafts by other writers. Draft material can also be found within the journals of Series I and the letters of Series II.
Series IV: The Printed Materials Series consists of four subseries of materials collected by Ed Smith: subseries A consists of monographs arranged alphabetically by author, subseries B consists of periodicals arranged alphabetically by title, subseries C contains catalogs for art shows arranged chronologically, and subseries D is miscellaneous printed materials arranged chronologically.
There is one large flat oversize box of material removed from Series II, and one large flat oversize box of material removed from Series III.
Other books and periodicals owned by Ed Smith have been separated out and moved to the stacks of the Fales Downtown Collection.
Arrangement
Ed Smith maintained his own combined subject and correspondence files, which he kept in folders arranged alphabetically, occasionally by first name, more often by last name, and by subject. His original arrangement has been kept in Series II. Where no folders existed for loose materials, new subject or correspondence files were created and interfiled with Smith's. Folders that were not part of Smith's arrangement scheme are indicated by brackets around the title.
Materials are arranged chronologically within the folders, except in the [flyers] folder wherein the mostly undated material is arranged by venue
Missing Title
Series I: Journals/Notebooks
Series II: Correspondence and Subject Series
Series III: Drafts, Production Materials, Final Published Work
Series IV: Printed Matierals
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Dennis Cooper Papers (MSS.085)
Tim Dlugos Papers (MSS.087)
Separated Material
The following published materials have been separated and individually catalogued into the Fales' Downtown Print and Periodicals Collection. Call numbers for these items can be located through Bobcat, NYU's online catalog.
Monographs removed to the Downtown Collection:
Abbott, Steve: Holy Terror (Freedom, CA: The Crossing Press, 1989)
Abbott, Steve: Lives of the Poets (San Francisco: Black Star Series, 1987)
Abbott, Steve: Skinny Trip to a Far Place (San Francisco: e.g. a literary press, 1988)
Abbott, Steve: Wrecked Hearts (San Francisco: Dancing Rock Press, 1978)
Barry, Lynda: Naked Ladies Naked Ladies Naked Ladies Coloring Book (Seattle, WA: The Real Comet Press, 1984)
Carr, Robin: Black Jello (Los Angeles, Little Savage Press, 1992)
Carr, Robin: Mudpies (Los Angeles, Little Savage Press, 1984)
Clinton, Michelle T.: High Blood Pressure (Los Angeles, West End Press, 1986)
Cooper, Dennis: Antoine Monnier (Sherman Oaks, CA: Anon Press, 1978
D'Allesandra, Sam: Slippery Sins (San Francisco: Ice Press, 1983)
DeLynn, Jane: Bad Sex is Good (New York: Pantheon Books, 1990)
DeLynn, Jane: In Thrall (New York: Clarkson N. Potter Inc., 1982)
DeLynn, Jane: Leash (Los Angeles and New York: Semiotext(e), 2002)
DeLynn, Jane: Some Do (New York, Macmillan, 1978)
Equi, Elaine: The Corners of the Mouth (Culver City, CA: Iridescence, 1986)
Ferrari, Mary: The Isle of the Little God (New York: The Kulchur Foundation, 1981)
Fisher, Harrison: Curtains (Washington, DC: The Word Works, Inc., 1980)
Flanagan, Bob: Bob Flanagan: Super-Masochist. Re/Search People Series, vol. 1(San Francisco: Re/Search Publications, 1993)
Flanagan, Bob: The Kid is the Man (Hermosa Beach, CA: Bombshelter Press, 1978)
Flanagan, Bob: The Pain Journal (Los Angeles: Semiotext(e), 2000)
Friedman, Michael: Special Capacity (New York, Intermezzo Press, 1992)
Gerstler, Amy and Smith, Alexis: Past Lives (Santa Monica: authors and Santa Monica Museum of Art, 1989)
Gerstler, Amy: Early Heaven (San Francisco, Ouija Madness Press, 1984)
Gerstler, Amy: Primitive Man (Madras and New York: Hanuman Books, 1987)
Gerstler, Amy: The True Bride (Santa Monica: The Lapis Press, 1986)
Gerstler, Amy: Yonder (Los Angeles: Little Caesar Press, 1981)
Hall, Steven: Black Watch (New York: Intermezzo Press, 1991)
Hall, Steven: My Newport (New York: Shell Press, 1981)
Hall, Steven: Style (New York: Shell Press, 1980)
Koertge, Ron: Diary Cows (Los Angeles: Little Caesar Press, 1981)
Krusoe, James: ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ (Los Angeles: Illuminati, 1984)
Krusoe, James: Small Pianos (Los Angeles: Momentum Press, 1978)
Lehman, David (editor): Ecstatic Occasions, Expedient Forms (New York: Collier Books, 1987)
Maw Shein Win: Tales of a Lonely Meat Eater (Long Beach, CA: Lemon Fingers Press, 1991)
McKuen, Rod: In Someone's Shadow (New York: Cheval Books and Random House, 1969)
McKuen, Rod: In Someone's Shadow (New York: Cheval Books and Random House, 1969)
McKuen, Rod: Listen to the Warm (New York: Random House pocket edition, 1963-1969)
McKuen, Rod: Listen to the Warm (New York: Random House, 1963-1967)
McKuen, Rod: Lonesome Cities (New York, Random House, 1965-1968)
McKuen, Rod: Moment to Moment (New York, Simon and Schuster/Cheval Books, 1974)
McKuen, Rod: Stanyan Street and Other Sorrows (Hollywood, CA: Cheval/Stanyan, 1966)
McKuen, Rod: Stanyan Street and Other Sorrows (New York: Random House, 1967)
McKuen, Rod: Suspension Bridge (New York: Harper and Row, 1984)
McKuen, Rod: With Love (Los Angeles: Stanyan Books and Random House, 1968)
McWilliams, Peter: I Have Loved (Allen Park, Michigan: Versemonger Press, 1968)
Meltzer, Richard: Richard Meltzer's Guide to the Ugliest Buildings of Los Angeles (Los Angeles, Illuminati, 1984)
Northup, Harry E.: Enough the Great Running Chapel (Santa Monica: Momentum Press, 1982)
Notley, Alice: How Spring Comes (West Branch Iowa: The Toothpaste Press, 1981)
Podesta, Patty (editor): Resolution: A Critique of Video Art (Los Angeles: Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions, 1986)
Rexroth, Kenneth (translator): One Hundred More Poems from the Japanese (New York: New Directions, 1976)
Rexroth, Kenneth (translator): One Hundred Poems from the Japanese (New York: New Directions, 1971)
Schutz, Susan Polis: Peace Flows From the Sky (Boulder, CO: Blue Mountain Arts Inc, 1974)
Sexton, Anne: The Death Notebooks (Boston, Houghton Mifflin, 1974)
Shaw, Jim: Life and Death (The End is Here Publications, 1981)
Sherwood, Rachel: Mysteries of Afternoon and Evening (Chatsworth, CA: Sherwood Press/Yarmouth Press, 1981)
Smith, Ed: Dwasline Road (Clifton, NJ: Gaede's Pond Press, 1983) (note: the author is a different Ed Smith from the Ed Smith of these papers)
Smith, Ed: Fantasyworld (Venice, CA: Cold Calm Press, 1983)
Smith, Ed: Tim's Bunnies and Other Poems (Los Angeles: Cold Calm Press, 1988)
Tom of Finland: Cops in Tom's Drawings (Los Angeles: Tom of Finland)
Turrell, Occluded Front (Larkspur Landing, CA: The Lapis Press, 1985)
various authors: Atrophy! (Los Angeles: Blue Funk Press, 1987)
Vinogrand, Julia: Street Mystery (J/S Press, 1985)
Periodicals removed to Downtown Collection:
Actual Size, no. 1
Blind Date, no. 3, 1988
Comet, vol. 1, no. 1, Spring 2000
Comet, vol. 2, no. 1, Spring 2001
Common Lives/Lesbian Lives, no. 1, Fall 1981
Damage no. 5, Spring 1980
Damage no. 9, September/October 1980
The Daughters of the Rectangle, no. 2, 1981
Destroy All Monsters vol. 2, no. 6, 1979
Destroy All Monsters no. 5
Destroy All Monsters no number, no date
Female FYI, no. 5
Flat Disk Newsletter, vol. 4, no. 16 [1981]
Flat Disk Newsletter [1982]
Flip Side, no. 9, [1978]
Flip Side, no. 15, 1979
Flip Side, no. 18, 1980
Flip Side, no. 57, Fall 1988
Forehead, vol. 1, 1987
Forehead, vol. 2, 1990
Gandhabba, no. 4, 1986
The Headbanger, no. 6, 1983
Heavy Metal Hardware no. 11
Insurgence no. 1, 1984
Lemon Fingers Emerge, no. 2
Lemon Fingers Emerge, no. 3
Lemon Fingers Emerge, no. 4, 1987
Magazine, vol. 12, no. 3, Winter 1982
Magazine, vol. 13, no. 1, Winter 1983
Magazine, vol. 13, no. 2, Spring 1983
Magazine, vol. 13, no. 3, Summer 1983
Magazine, vol. 14, no. 1, Winter 1983-84
Magazine, vol. 14, no. 2, Spring 1984
Nude Erections, no. 2, 1985
On-Slaught, no. 2, 1982
Poetry Project, no. 110
Poetry Project, no. 111
Puncture,
Scratch Magazine, vol. 1, no. 4, 14 July 1983
Scratch Magazine, vol. 1, no. 24, 2 December 1983
Shiny: The Magazine of the Future, no. 5, 1990
Shiny: The Magazine of the Future, no. 6, spring/summer 1991
Slash, vol. 1, no. 12
Slash, vol. 2, no. 7
Slash, vol. 3, no. 3
Slash, vol. 3, no. 4, 1980
Snap, vol. 1, no. 1, 1982
Spazz, vol. 1, no. 9, 1994
Spectacle Magazine, nos. 5/6, Fall 1986
Stop, vol. 2, 1990
Stuff Magazine, no. 36, 1982
Stuff Magazine, no. 39, 1983
Umezowea, no. 6
Whispering Campaign (contains 3 poems by Ed Smith)
Zomoid Illustories by Jim Shaw, vol. 1, no. 27, 1985
Zyzzyva, vol. 2, no. 1, Spring 1986
Zyzzyva, vol. 2, no. 4, Winter 1986-87
Zyzzyva, vol. 3, no. 3, Fall 1987
Zyzzyva, vol. 3, no. 4, Winter 1987-88
New York (N.Y.).; Little magazines.; Black-and-white photographs.; Announcements.; Correspondence.; Posters.; Poets, American -- 20th century.; Los Angeles (Calif.) |x Intellectual life |y 20th century.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Color negatives.; Artists and community -- United States; Color photographs.; Scripts (documents); Notebooks; Manuscripts for publication.; Magazines (Periodicals); Authors, American -- 20th century.; Invitations.; Los Angeles (Calif.); Diaries; American literature -- 20th century.; Fliers (printed matter); Color slides.; Clippings (information artifacts); Newspapers.; Books.; Pearce, Celia; Hall, Steven; Gerstler, Amy; Flanagan, Bob, 1952-1996; Williams, Mary; Cooper, Dennis, 1953-; Beyond Baroque Literary Arts Center; Baumgart, Ingrid; Arnold, Skip, 1957-; Shirai, Mio, 1962-
- Series I: Journals/Notebooks
  Scope and Contents note
  The Journals/Notebooks Series consists of spiral notebooks, bound notebooks, loose pages, and legal pads containing diary entries, drafts of poetry and correspondence, and business notes, arranged chronologically. The date reflects the date the journal begins.
  - Journals/Notebooks, 16 February 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 1 January 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Journals/Notebooks, [late 1970's] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Journals/Notebooks, [late 1970's] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 1 February 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 10 February 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages Ed Smith foldered and labeled "Old Work Diary", 2 November 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 4 November 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 14 January 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 10 February 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 16 March 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Journals/Notebooks 7 April 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 7 July 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 26 August 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 10 November 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Journals/Notebooks, [late 1982] (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Journals/Notebooks, [late 1982] (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 16 February 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 27 December 1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 8 February 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 26 February 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 8 August 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 22 October 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 31 January 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 23 October 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 17 October 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 26 July 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 8 August 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 3 November 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 14 June 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 24 September 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 12 April 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 2 July 1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 6 July 1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 8 September 1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 28 September 1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 29 September 1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 4 October 1989 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 7 October 1989 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages dated, chronological 1978-1988 (bulk 1981-1986) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages undated, [1980's] (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages undated, [1980's] (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages undated, [1980's] (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages undated, [1980's] (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Journals/Notebooks, [1980's] (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Journals/Notebooks, index cards tied together with string, [1980's] (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Journals/Notebooks, July 1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 28 November 1990 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 17 November 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 31 January 1992 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 12 September 1992 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 23 June 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 4 August 1994 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 18 March 1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 4 April 1995 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 15 July 1997 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 14 August 1997 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 19 November 1998 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 16 February 1999 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 24 September 1999 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 26 October 1999 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 21 February 2000 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Journals/Notebooks, December 2000 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 10 December 2000 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 19 January 2001 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose papers that had been clipped together as a set, 9 March 2001 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 12 September 2001 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 16 October 2001 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 26 November 2001 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Journals/Notebooks, draft of letter to Mike Wallace, [2001] (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 7 January 2002 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 6 June 2002 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 21 July 2002 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 30 October 2002 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 15 December 2002 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 18 December 2002 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 23 January 2003 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 7 February 2003 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 17 February 2003 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 17 March 2003 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 1 April 2003 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages that had been clipped together, 14 April 2003 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 17 April 2003 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 31 May 2003 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 2 December 2003 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 25 February 2004 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 28 February 2004 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 6 May 2004 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 6 May 2004 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 11 May 2004 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 7 July 2004 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 18 October 2004 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 25 October 2004 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Journals/Notebooks, 21 December 2004 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Journals/Notebooks, loose pages filed chronologically, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Journals/Notebooks, post-it notes., undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Journals/Notebooks., undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Series II: Correspondence and Subject Series
  This series consists of interfiled correspondence folders and subject folders, arranged alphabetically by correspondent or subject, and chronologically within the folders. Ed Smith's original arrangement has been kept, and thus alphebetization is occasionally by first name, more often by last name, and by subject. Where no folders existed for loose materials, new subject or correspondence files were created and interfiled with Smith's. Folders that were not part of Smith's arrangement scheme are indicated by brackets around the title. The folders contain correspondence, flyers, photographs, and ephemera.
  - Advertising [Ads Ed Smith clipped from magazines], undated (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Advertising [Material related to Giant Superstore - includes photographs], 1986 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - [Advertising Work] [copy Smith wrote for movies], 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Allegra, 1987-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Angela [Schill], 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Angela [Schill], [includes photograph], undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Apex Novelties, undated (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Arnold, Skip [includes photographs] [additional material separated to oversized box], 1982-1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 119, Box 10)
  - Banks, Pam, 1979-1983, undated (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - [Barney Magazine], 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Baumgart, Ingrid, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Baumgart, Ingrid, [notes to each other], [1982-1985] (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Baumgart, Ingrid [Raszebrae materials - flyers, press, songs, playlists, etc.], [1982-1985] (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Baumgart, Ingrid [acidic materials - newsprint etc.], [1982-1985] (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Baumgart, Ingrid [photographs and negatives], [1982-1985] (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Baumgart, Ingrid [resume, research paper, printed material], undated (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Baumgart, Ingrid [miscellaneous], undated (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Bell, Michele, undated (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Beth [Herzhaft], 1987-1990, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - [Beyond Baroque], 1981-1998, undated [bulk 1981-1984] (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Biz [resumes, business letters, business cards], 1980-2004, undated (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - [Blue's Clues], 2000-2003, undated (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Book City 1978 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Clinton, Michelle, 1982-1987, undated (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - ComicCon, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - ComicCon, 1989-1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Cooper, Dennis [includes photograph], 1983-1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Correspondence '88, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - [CSAI], 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Cypis, Dorit, 1982-1987 (bulk 1987) (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Dawson, Kathleen, 1979-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Dick [photographs], undated (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Dori [Seda] [includes photographs], 1986-1999 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Ferris, Elaine [includes photograph], 1978-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Flanagan, Bob [includes photographs], 1982-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - [Flyers and a few programs - Al's Bar, Anti-Club, Bebop, C.A.S.H., Cathay de Grand, CBGB, Club 57, Club Lingerie, Continental, Exile, Foundation for Arts Resources, Hong Kong Cafe, Intersection for the Arts, LACE, Lhasa Club, Madame Wong's, Mercury Arts Center, Metropolis, Newport Harbor Art Museum, Old Venice Jail, Piezo Electric, S.I.R., Vex, Whisky, Zero Zero][3 oversize flyers (posters) separated to oversize box - Cal Arts, Lace, San Diego State University], mostly undated, bulk 1980's (Box 4, Folder 147, Box 10)
  - Funeral Booklet for Ed Smith, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Genee [additional material separated to oversized box], 1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 149, Box 10)
  - Germs [contracts and correspondence with the band], 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 150)